

export const quizdataS = {
  totalQuestions: 6,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      topic: '첫인사 하기',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['고맙습니다', '농인입니다', '안녕하세요', '저는'],
      correctAnswer: '농인입니다',
      image: '/농인.GIF',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      topic: '첫인사 하기',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['우리', '안녕하세요', '손', '내일'],
      correctAnswer: '안녕하세요',
      image: '/안녕하세요.GIF',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      topic: '첫인사 하기',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['고맙습니다', '월요일', '안녕하세요', '저는'],
      correctAnswer: '저는',
      image: '/저는.GIF',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      topic: '첫인사 하기',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['청인입니다', '농인입니다', '아니에요', '음식'],
      correctAnswer: '청인입니다',
      image: '/청인.GIF',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      topic: '첫인사 하기',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['가렵다', '만나서 반가워요', '새로워요', '당신'],
      correctAnswer: '만나서 반가워요',
      image: '/만나서반갑습니다.GIF',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      topic: '첫인사 하기',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['무엇', '아니다', '원하다', '하나'],
      correctAnswer: '무엇',
      image: '/무엇.GIF',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      topic: '우리 가족',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['어제', '결혼', '할머니', '덥다'],
      correctAnswer: '할머니',
      image: '/할머니.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      topic: '우리 가족',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['만남', '모이다', '끝났어요?', '결혼하셨나요?'],
      correctAnswer: '결혼하셨나요?',
      image: '/결혼하셨나요.gif',
    },

    {
      id: 9,
      topic: '우리 가족',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['엄마', '아빠', '부모님', '언니'],
      correctAnswer: '아빠',
      image: '/아빠.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      topic: '우리 가족',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['여동생', '남동생', '언니/누나', '형/오빠'],
      correctAnswer: '언니/누나',
      image: '/언니_누나.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      topic: '우리 가족',
      question: '제시된 수어의 올바른 뜻을 고르세요',
      answers: ['전화', '가족', '독립하다', '집'],
      correctAnswer: '가족',
      image: '/가족.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      topic: '지숫자',
      question: '제시된 수어와 일치하는 숫자를 고르세요',
      answers: ['5', '10', '1', '6'],
      correctAnswer: '5',
      image: '/5.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      topic: '지숫자',
      question: '제시된 수어와 일치하는 숫자를 고르세요',
      answers: ['8', '7', '3', '12'],
      correctAnswer: '8',
      image: '/8.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      topic: '지숫자',
      question: '제시된 수어와 일치하는 숫자를 고르세요',
      answers: ['1', '0', '10', '9'],
      correctAnswer: '10',
      image: '/10.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      topic: '지숫자',
      question: '제시된 수어와 일치하는 숫자를 고르세요',
      answers: ['0', '5', '10', '9'],
      correctAnswer: '9',
      image: '/9.gif',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      topic: '지숫자',
      question: '제시된 수어와 일치하는 숫자를 고르세요',
      answers: ['4', '1', '6', '9'],
      correctAnswer: '4',
      image: '/4.gif',
    },
  ],
};